what's good y'all we are chilling like we always do right here at the amanda seals show i'm amanda
seals joined by dj nails what's happening on this thirsty thursday well what's happened is that we
have been discussing rapper gunna who recently snitched and got out of jail in the ysl young
thug rico case right now as a result a lot of rappers have turned their backs on gunna including
jim jones who said this you know we were going to play the clip but i don't got time to play the
clip i don't feel like playing the clip jim jones basically saying well you know when you do that
you gonna have some you know clapbacks to that and so you really shouldn't be snitching okay so that's
your summation of what jim jones was saying what i'm more interested in is y'all the y'all means out
there who might be posted up right now listening to the show and how you feel about this snitching
scenario hey amanda man first thing i want to say is i love what you said man you gotta be committed
to something man if you're not going to be committed to something you shouldn't even get
involved with it you know i'm saying it's a lot of people that don't agree with street rules and
people that agree with them wholeheartedly you get to you don't want to be in the street you don't
worry about the rules don't get in the streets you can snitch all you want to if you ain't in the
street civilians can snitch but you decided to become a person who was expected not to so that's
where it all come in and he definitely snitched like my man said man you got co-defendant you don't
keep on key deals if there's three of y'all going down for a crime and you say you ain't do it it
can be simple as saying i ain't do it that means one of the other two didn't drive snitching man like
his whole joint like come on man he implicated them as a gang i'm calling about the gunner situation man
what you said is right a lot of people they they wanted to live this life but they can't take what
comes with it and the thing is it's like nobody's teaching these kids about what happens behind them
walls nobody goes through the daily motions of not that they're like yeah i don't know what comes with
that life i have it the y'all means have spoken and this from people who they've been through it and
they're in it you know you can hear it in your voice facts facts homeboys homeboys like we need
to bring back scared straight these kids don't know what go on back there that's why they acting
all reckless and then when the shit go down they don't know what to do listen i really appreciate
all of you all calling in for for the basic reason of that lets me know y'all are listening and we got
real ones listening and i love the fact that we have cats that are from very all different lifestyles we
have people listening from all different lifestyles all over the country all over the world listening
that just makes me feel so good about the show that we're doing the content that we're doing
and i love that we're able to take this this conversation and expand it to folks who are like
nah this is how it works but you know what the thing is nails i think when it comes down to snitching
a lot of them are making the valid point that if you are not in it it ain't snitching if you're not in
the streets it ain't snitching you see something say something like that's what it is but if you
signed up for it and then you turn when you get caught that's what makes a snitching yep yep you
live by the code if you in it you live by the code if you break the code guess what you got to deal
with the consequences and the consequences in gunna's case are that people are going to unfollow
him on instagram and if that's the least of his code switching situations then you know what maybe
then he is probably all right with his decision again we want to hear from you all so make sure to
hit us up 1-855-2626-328 we got more for you right here at the amanda seal show don't go nowhere